waste.uk.com 2015-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Sandbag treats personal information that they collect on this and other web sites, including information related to your past use of the site such as previous order details.

Personal information is personally identifiable information about you such as your name, address, email address, phone number and so on, that is not normally publically available.

This policy does not apply to companies that Sandbag does not control, or to any third parties that Sandbag does not employ or manage. In particular, This site may have links to external sites that Sandbag does not own or control and you should look at each such site's own privacy policy to see how your personal information is managed.

**Information Collection and Use**

Sandbag collects personal information when you register with Sandbag and when you use Sandbag's site.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code. Once you register with Sandbag **and** sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Sandbag collects information about your transactions with us.

Sandbag automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Sandbag cookie information, and the page you request.

Sandbag uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide **anonymous** reporting for our Management team and or our Web team.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Sandbag does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies except to provide products or services you've requested from our site(s), when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Sandbag's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

If Sandbag is acquired by or merged with another company, Sandbag will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies**

Sandbag may set and access Sandbag cookies on your computer and uses cookies in connection with Sandbag's site for your benefit.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

You can edit your Sandbag account Information, including your address and contact details at any time. You cannot directly change the name, address, contact details and other details of existing orders, but can contact Sandbag to change order details if you need to.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Sandbag Store such as relevant service announcements and administrative messages, that are considered part of your Sandbag account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. You can remove your Sandbag Account which will stop you being sent these messages. Please note that if you place an order with the site, that Sandbag will keep a permanent record of your details as entered at the time of the order.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. We also comply fully with the UK Data Protection Act.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Sandbag may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Sandbag account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. If Sandbag choose to send an email, you will be sent the email even if you are unsubscribed from receiving general emails from us.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions on how Sandbag may improve, please contact:
